ezthemes.com 2000-12-05

# Privacy Statement - EZthemes

## Privacy Statement for EZthemes

MozlSoft has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: EZthemes. 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. We use cookies to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. 

NOTE ON COOKIES:   
A cookie is a small data file that certain Web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you've visited. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. 

Registration: when you register as a member, EZthemes uses a cookie to store a unique, random user ID. We use this ID to identify you as a member without you having to log on each time. 

Ads: EZtheme's advertising partners may deliver a one-time cookie to better track ad impressions and click rates. 

Tracking: EZtheme's statistical tracking software delivers cookies to enable us to determine how many people visit the site. 

You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use the EZthemes site. 

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address). We use visitor contact information from the registration form to send the user promotional material from some of our partners. The visitor's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

This site contains links to other sites. EZthemes is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**Some of our 'site partners' and 'ad partners' include:**

PostMasterDirect, an opt-in mailing list maintenance company - Your name and/or email are NEVER passed on to this company unless you SPECIFICALLY request to be added though the DESIGNATED PostMasterDirect signup page 

Flycast. To find out more about how Flycast manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to <http://www.flycast.com/about_us/about-privacy.html>. 

EveryOne.net, who provide our users with FREE EMAIL. 

**Your name and/or email are NEVER passed on to these companies unless you SPECIFICALLY request to be added though the DESIGNATED signup pages**

From time to time some of our advertising partners may request your email address or other personal information. Please refer to their privacy policy for their specific use of this information). 

Our online surveys is anonymous and never ask visitors for contact information (like their email address). However our newsletter does require this information. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

## Security

Mailing lists are maintained by our mailing list partner, Dundee.net. We rely on their security to maintain the integrity of a mailing lists. 

## Choice/Opt-Out

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

  1. You can Email our List manager per instructions with each newsletter. 
  2. You can notify us by email giving your full subscription information as provided upon subscription. 

## Correct/Update

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

  1. email [support@ezthemes.com](mailto:support@ezthemes.com)

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact Steve Mosley MozlSoft 4802 East Ray Road PMB 23144 Phoenix, AZ, 85044 [steve@mozlsoft.com](mailto:support@ezthemes.com)

* * *
